Jen knocked him down on purpose. Championship.
What the hell is this?
You're gonna beat me on purpose?
If you let her get to the top next time, I'll take my side.
But it would make all the difference if I could get the right one out.
I want to keep it steady.
You keep saying you want to take this side, but you should take this side.
I want to take this side, but I want to keep the balance up.
Why can't I take this side?
Win.
What? Why are you stopping here?
Did we stop?
It kind of stopped.
What's the point of killing if you're just going to follow one?
I'm going down.
That's weird, Aina.
It's too much.
What's the point of killing if you can't follow the one you're following?
I doubt it, aina.
Oh, my God.
I'm going to fall over.
This...
Ichikawa.
Yes!
Ichikawa
Yeah, yeah.
No, no, no.
I can't do it.
I'm fine-tuning, fine-tuning, fine-tuning.
I'm fine-tuning it.
I can't, I can't, I can't.
I can't.
Oh, my God.
There it is.
It's possible.
It's not a little suspicious.
The moment you said it was weird like this...
I probably just put the towel back on.
Get it in order.
I don't want to do that right now.
It wasn't me.
It's really not me.
I'm just... I'm just...
It's not weird like this.
Suspicious.
Oh, my God.
I'm going down.
I can't do it.
He's fine-tuning it, fine-tuning it.
I'm fine-tuning it.
I can't. I can't. I can't.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
The end part is the other way around.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Go for it!
Wait, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Suzuki.
Suzuki
If it's meaningless words, I don't need them anymore
Come now, come now Saori Yoimi
You...
Eh, so...
I can't do it!
It's true!
That's why there's a lot in the middle from this side.
No, it's too hard.
Oh, I did it like that.
Careful, that way.
I'm...
No, why?
What? It's all hard!
I'm really trying, but it's like that.
Oh, wait.
I don't know, guys.
I don't know.
Wow, Suzuki, that's weird.
Actually, I chewed the tort.
But I'm doing hard news.
Doubtful.
Try it. Try it.
Eh, I don't know, guys.
I don't know.
Oh, Suzuki, that's weird.
I'm telling you, man.
Actually, I chewed the tort.
But I'm on hard news.
Doubtful.
Try it, try it.
Sober.
I was gonna say that, but it slipped out.
Oh, man, I wonder if it'll come around.
Oh, no, it's too tough now.
Take it down already.
Please take me down already.
I'll pray for you.
I don't think we're gonna make it.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, I'm going in.
Oh, I'm coming, baby.
Yeah, baby.
It's done.
It's over.
It's the end of the year.
Take it down, take it down.
Wow, that's a sensitive position you're in.
Yay.
Yikes.
But, I mean, isn't it about time?
If they're doing this on purpose.
That's where the action is.
Okay, it's about time.
Get comfortable.
I'm just gonna take it down like a normal person, you know?
Ease back into it.
That's how we're going to act.
Oh, I think I got it.
No, but it's working.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That looks good.
Stop it. Don't pull it out.
Is it done?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, my God!
That scared the shit out of me.
I fell down.
I know, right?
I thought I could do it.
It only took one.
Oh!
You scared me.
I fell down.
I know, right?
I thought I could make it.
Well, let's see...
So you're the one who beat him, Hana-chan.
Okay.
Hana-chan, pick someone.
Hmmm...
Okay, Moka.
Oh, yes, so it's Moeka-chan.
Did Hana beat you for real or on purpose?
Please judge.
If I'm wrong on this, Moka wins.
It's the worst that they tightened it up.
It's true.
Please judge whether Hana was stiff or deliberate in knocking him down.
GACHI!
This one forgot the other one. The other one forgot about it.
Really? Final answer.
Yeah, I don't think so.
No way.
What makes you think I'm serious?
I thought it was a little suspicious because of the flowery, stature-oriented part.
It's not suspicious.
Don't worry about it.
Who are you talking about?
It's not suspicious. I'm sure, I'm sure.
If he's serious, he's just doing it.
I don't know. I want to go again.
What did you think it was? What did you think it was?
I don't think it was the Joker.
I was serious.
I was.
Oh!
Happy birthday.
No? No, no, no.
Wow!
Was that Moeka?
It was Moeka?
Stamps lay.
I was pretty sure it was Moeka.
If nothing happened like this, then she must be really weak.
Yeah, that's why I thought she'd think so and find out.
Yeah, yeah.
Yes, I was in a hurry to do something because Moka was too lazy to do it and I was afraid she would find out,
So it was this way? You said you were going to plant something.
Yes, I was going to plant something.
When Moka said "Moeka," I said, "Yay, I did it!
He said, "I won.
We did something.
You did?
Yeah, I did.
It's beautiful.
Yes, we did it.
Nose fly, nose fly.
Moehka, that's weird.
I've been doing it for a long time.
I couldn't blame her. I wanted to blame him more.
I wanted to blame you more for the ones that stopped.
I didn't have much to evaluate.
I wanted to do it.
Why did you stop here?
Did it stop?
We kind of stopped.
I thought I'd be exposed the moment we made the split.
Oh, I see.
Yes, I thought that I would win if I let someone else beat me.
No, I was wrong.
So, I'm going to say it's Hana-chan's punishment game,
I'm going to put Moka in the Chiba base.
Moka-chan, you went.
I'm going to put in a lot of them.
I'll put them all in.
I wore my new sweatshirt.
That's okay, that's enough.
Yes!
You rushed me.
Surprise, you rushed it.
That was the worst.
No, we can change it from here to this.
It's boiling water to the stomach.
Wow.
It's cold, isn't it?
Let's go.